<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/project-plan.xsl"?><!--
    Copyright (c) 2008 Wind River Systems, Inc. and others.
    All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials
    are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0
    which accompanies this distribution, and is available at
    http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html
   
    Contributors:
    Martin Oberhuber (Wind River) - initial API and implementation
 -->

<plan plan-format="1.0">
  <release projectid="dsdp.tm" version="3.0"/>
    <introduction><![CDATA[
The Target Management Project provides data models, frameworks and tools 
for working with remote computer systems.
The main deliverable is the Remote System Explorer (RSE), a feature-rich 
integrated perspective and toolkit for seamlessly working on
remote systems. Besides that, we deliver flexible, re-usable 
components for Networking and Target Management that run stand-alone
or integrated with RSE.
<p>
In terms of interfaces to other Eclipse projects, we provide an
Eclipse Filesystem (EFS) provider to allow remote resources be
mapped into an Eclipse Workspace, and a CDT Remote Launch integration.
</p>  
    ]]>
  </introduction>
  <release_deliverables><![CDATA[
<ul>
	<li><b>Target Management source code release</b>, available as versions tagged "R3_0" in the project's<ul>
		<li><a href="http://dev.eclipse.org/viewcvs/index.cgi/org.eclipse.tm.rse/?cvsroot=DSDP_Project">RSE CVS Repository</a>,</li>
		<li><a href="http://dev.eclipse.org/viewcvs/index.cgi/org.eclipse.tm.core/?cvsroot=DSDP_Project">TM Core CVS Repository</a>, and</li>
		<li><a href="http://dev.eclipse.org/viewcvs/index.cgi/org.eclipse.tm.tcf/trunk/?root=DSDP_SVN">TM TCF SVN Repository</a>.</li>
	</ul></li>
	<li><b>Remote System Explorer (RSE):</b><ul>
	   <li>RSE SDK (includes runtime, user and programmer documentation, with sources) (downloadable).</li>
	   <li>RSE client runtime binaries (split up by protocol, includes user documentation) (downloadable).</li>
	   <li>RSE dstore server runtime (downloadable).</li>
	   <li>RSE User Actions and Compile Commands (downloadable).</li>
	   <li>RSE CDT Launch Integration (downloadable).</li>
	   <li>RSE tutorial code and examples (downloadable).</li>
       <li>RSE unit test framework and tests (downloadable).</li>
    </ul></li>
    <li><b>Stand-alone components:</b><ul>
	   <li>TM Terminal SDK (includes runtime, user and programmer documentation, with sources) (downloadable).</li>
	   <li>TM Discovery SDK (includes runtime, user and programmer documentation, with sources) (downloadable).</li>
	   <li>Redistribution of Apache Commons Net 1.4.1 and Jakarta ORO 2.0.8 (downloadable through the Orbit project).</li>
    </ul></li>
    <li><b>Incubating components:</b><ul>
	   <li>RSE Terminal Integration (runtime and sources) (downloadable).</li>
	   <li>RSE WinCE Subsystems and RAPI wrappers (runtime and sources) (downloadable).</li>
    </ul></li>
</ul>
<b>Notes:</b>
All stand-alone components will have an integration part that makes
them work inside the RSE framework. For that reason, there are no
downloadable stand-alone component tests, but the RSE unit test
component will also have tests for the stand-alone components.
<p>
The incubating <b>TCF</b> component is not going to produce downloadable
artifacts for the TM 3.0 reelease.
  ]]></release_deliverables>
  <release_milestones>
    <preamble><![CDATA[      
Release milestone will be occurring at roughly 6 week intervals,
and will be aligned with the
<a href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/ganymede.php">
Ganymede Simultaneous Release</a> train.
Milestone names start with M3 in order to clarify this
relationship.
    ]]></preamble>
    <milestone date="11/14/2007" milestone="M3" bugzilla=""><![CDATA[ 3.0M3 ]]></milestone>
    <milestone date="1/7/2008" milestone="M4" bugzilla=""><![CDATA[ 3.0M4 ]]></milestone>
    <milestone date="2/18/2008" milestone="M5" bugzilla=""><![CDATA[ 3.0M5 ]]></milestone>
    <milestone date="4/7/2008" milestone="M6" bugzilla=""><![CDATA[ 3.0M6 (API Freeze)]]></milestone>
    <milestone date="5/6/2008" milestone="M7" bugzilla=""><![CDATA[ 3.0M7 (Feature Freeze)]]></milestone>
    <milestone date="5/20/2008" milestone="RC1" bugzilla=""><![CDATA[ 3.0RC1 ]]></milestone>
    <milestone date="5/27/2008" milestone="RC2" bugzilla=""><![CDATA[ 3.0RC2 ]]></milestone>
    <milestone date="6/3/2008" milestone="RC3" bugzilla=""><![CDATA[ 3.0RC3 ]]></milestone>
    <milestone date="6/10/2008" milestone="RC4" bugzilla=""><![CDATA[ 3.0RC4 ]]></milestone>
    <postamble><![CDATA[
A detailed <a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/TM_3.0_Ramp_down_Plan">
TM 3.0 Ramp down Plan</a> towards the release is available especially for the Eclipse 
<a href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/ganymede.php">
Ganymede Simultaneous Release</a> integration.
<p>
The target date for availability of Target Management 3.0 is:</p>
<ul>
	<li>Wednesday June 25, 2008 - TM 3.0 Release date (with Ganymede)</li>
</ul>
    ]]></postamble>
  </release_milestones>
  <target_environments><![CDATA[
In order to remain current, each Eclipse release is designed to run on
reasonably current versions of the underlying operating environments.
</p>
<p>The Target Management Project 3.0 depends upon on the Eclipse Platform 3.4.
Various sub components also depend on other Eclipse Projects, namely
the C/C++ Development Tools (CDT) 4.0 or later, and the Eclipse Modeling
Framework (EMF) 2.3 or later. 
For this release, the RSE sources will be written and compiled
against version 1.4.2 of the Java Platform APIs (i.e., Java 2 Platform,
Release 1.4.2 SE), and designed to run on version 1.4.2 of the Java
Runtime Environment, Standard Edition. Since Java 5 is also used as
Eclipse Reference Platform, some testing of Target Management will also
be done on Java 5.</p> 

<p>The Target Management deliverables will be tested and validated against a 
subset of the reference platforms listed in the 
<a href="http://www.eclipse.org/eclipse/development/eclipse_project_plan_3_4.html#TargetOperatingEnvironments">Eclipse Platform 3.4 Project Plan</a>
(this list is updated over the course of the release cycle).</p>

<table summary="Target Management Reference Platforms" style="width: 821px;"
border="1">
<tbody>
<tr bgcolor="#cccccc">
<th colspan="5">
<div align="center"><strong><font size="+1">Target Management Reference
Platforms</font></strong></div>
</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="205"><b>Operating system</b></td>
<td width="59"><b>OS version</b></td>
<td width="76"><b>Processor architecture</b></td>
<td width="59"><b>Window system</b></td>
<td width="453"><b>Java 2 Platform</b></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="205">Microsoft Windows</td>
<td width="59">XP</td>
<td width="76">x86-32</td>
<td width="59">Win32</td>
<td width="453"> Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14<br>
for Microsoft Windows </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="205">Microsoft Windows</td>
<td width="59">XP</td>
<td width="76">x86-32</td>
<td width="59">Win32</td>
<td width="453"> IBM 32-bit SDK for Windows,<br>
Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR5 </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="205">Red Hat Enterprise Linux</td>
<td width="59">WS 4 update 2</td>
<td width="76">x86-32</td>
<td width="59">GTK</td>
<td width="453"> Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14<br>
for Linux x86</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="205">SUSE Linux Enterprise Server</td>
<td width="59">10</td>
<td width="76">x86-32</td>
<td width="59">GTK</td>
<td width="453"> IBM 32-bit SDK for Linux on Intel architecture,<br>
Java 2 Technology Edition 1.4.2 SR7 </td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="205">Sun Solaris</td>
<td width="59">10</td>
<td width="76">SPARC</td>
<td width="59">GTK</td>
<td width="453">Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14<br>
for Solaris SPARC</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="205">Apple Mac OS X (<i>Secondary, see below</i>)</td>
<td width="59">10.5</td>
<td width="76">Power</td>
<td width="59">Carbon</td>
<td width="453">
Apple Java 2 Platform Standard Edition (J2SE) 5, service release 4
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

<p>The following Platforms have been discontinued as Reference Platforms
for TM 3.0: Microsoft Windows 2000, Ubuntu Linux, SuSE Linux Enterprise
Server 9, Solaris 9, and Mac OS X 10.4. 
We expect that TM still runs fine on these Platforms, but don't have
the resources and interested parties at hand to perform systematic
testing on them.<br/>
Apple Mac OS X 10.5 is considered a "secondary" Reference Platform
meaning that it does receive some amount of systematic testing but
doesn't enjoy quite the same priority for bug fixes as the other
Platforms.</p>

<p>Eclipse and Target Management undoubtedly run fine
in many operating environments beyond the reference platforms we test.
However, since we do not systematically test them we cannot vouch for them.
Problems encountered when running Target Management on a non-reference platform
that cannot be recreated on any reference platform will be given lower
priority than problems with running Target Management on a reference platform.</p>

<p>Although untested, Target Management should work fine on other OSes that 
support the same window system. For Win32: NT, 2000, Vista, and Server 
2003; SWT HTML viewer requires Internet Explorer 5 (or higher).
For GTK on other Linux systems: version 2.2.1 of the GTK+ widget toolkit
and associated libraries (GLib, Pango); SWT HTML viewer requires 
Mozilla 1.4GTK2. For more details, see the
<a href="http://www.eclipse.org/eclipse/development/eclipse_project_plan_3_4.html#TargetOperatingEnvironments">
Eclipse Project Plan 3.4 Reference Platforms</a>.</p>

<h4>
Datastore Agent Reference Platforms
</h4>
<p>The Datastore protocol is the default protocol shipped with RSE for
accessing remote file systems, process info and shells. It requires a
Datastore server (agent) running on the remote system.
This Datastore agent is shipped as plain Java Source Code together with the 
RSE distribution. It should run fine on any Java Platform, with additional
Data Miner Plug-ins that may be OS specific.</p>
<p>We will test and verify the Datastore agent on the following Reference
Platforms, which are a subset of the Platforms we test the RSE UI on:</p>
<ul>
<li>Red Hat Enterprise Linx 4, Intel x86, Sun 1.5.0_14 VM</li>
<li>SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 10, Intel x86, IBM 1.4.2 sr 7 VM</li>
<li>Apple Mac OS X 10.5, Power, Apple J2SE 5 sr 4 VM</li>
</ul>
  ]]>  <internationalization><![CDATA[
<p>The Remote System Explorer is designed as the basis for internationalized
products. The user interface elements provided by the RSE
components, including dialogs and error messages, are externalized. The
English strings are provided as the default resource bundles.
The default bundles will be localized to a subset of those
locales offered by the Platform. This plan will be updated to indicate
which locales will be provided and the timeframe for availability.</p>
    ]]></internationalization>
  </target_environments>
  <compatibility_with_previous_releases><![CDATA[
<p>In order to evolve APIs and especially foster more UI/Non-UI separation,
Target Management 3.0 will not be compatible with TM 2.0.</p>
<p>
  <strong>API Contract Compatibility:</strong> Target Management 3.0 will not be 
  compatible with TM 2.0.
</p>
<p><strong>Binary (plug-in) Compatibility:</strong> Target Management 3.0 will not be 
  compatible with TM 2.0. 
</p>
<p><strong>Source Compatibility:</strong> Target Management 3.0 will not be 
  compatible with TM 2.0, but a <em>Target Management 3.0 Migration Guide</em>
  will be published that explains how to port TM 2.0 applications to the 
  TM 3.0 APIs.
  In most cases, "organize imports" should be sufficient in order to
  update API usage to classes refactored for better UI/Non-UI separation.
  Downward source compatibility is not supported. 
</p>
<p><strong>Workspace Compatibility:</strong> We intend to keep Target Management
  3.0 upwards workspace-compatible with TM 2.0 unless noted. 
  This means that workspaces and projects created with TM 2.0 can be successfully 
  opened by Target Mangement 3.0 and upgraded to a 3.0 workspace.
  This includes especially TM 2.0 connection definitions, which may propagate 
  between workspaces via file copying or team repositories.
  User interface session state may be discarded when a workspace is upgraded.
  Downward workspace compatibility is not supported. 
  A workspace created (or opened) by a product based on TM 3.0 will be unusable 
  with a product based on TM 2.0.
</p>
<h3>API Contract</h3>
<p>APIs published for the Target Management 3.0 release will be carefully
reviewed prior to release, making use of "internal" packages for
unsupported and variable implementation classes. Client plug-ins that
directly depend on anything other than what is specified in the
published API are inherently unsupportable and receive no guarantees
about future compatibility. Refer to <i><a
	href="http://www.eclipse.org/articles/Article-API%20use/eclipse-api-usage-rules.html">How
to Use the Eclipse API</a></i> for information about how to write
compliant plug-ins.</p>
<!--
<p>
Though it is our goal to create stable APIs, being able to do so
depends on the amount of API feedback we will get from the community.
As described in <a href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/dev_process/eclipse-quality.php">
<i>Eclipse Quality APIs</i></a>, we will therefore mark all of our
APIs provisional. This removes the guarantee of 1.0 to 2.0 compatibility,
though we&#39;d strive to achieve that. We expect to get sufficient feedback
during the 1.0 to 2.0 development period to declare the APIs final.</p>
-->
  ]]></compatibility_with_previous_releases>
  <themes_and_priorities>
    <preamble><![CDATA[
<p>Plan items listed bleow were defined according to contributor requirements,
but in accordance with the Target Management
<a href="http://www.eclipse.org/dsdp/tm/doc/DSDPTM_Use_Cases_v1.1c.pdf">
Use Cases Document</a> and the DSDP and Eclipse
<a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/RequirementsCouncil06TP#Embedded_Device_Software">
Themes and Priorities</a> (Preliminary Roadmap v3)
set forth by the Eclipse Requirments Council.
Each plan item covers a feature or API that is to be added to the 
Target Management deliverables, or some aspect of the Target 
Management Project that is to be improved. Each plan item has its 
own entry in the Eclipse bugzilla database, with a title and a 
concise summary (usually a single paragraph) that explains the 
work item at a suitably high enough level so that everyone can 
readily understand what the work item is without having to understand
the nitty-gritty detail. 
</p>
<p>Not all plan items represent the same amount of work; some may be quite
large, others, quite small. Although some plan items are for work that is 
more pressing than others, the plan items appear in no particular order.
Use the
<a href="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&keywords_type=allwords&keywords=plan&classification=DSDP&product=Target+Management&bug_status=UNCONFIRMED&bug_status=NEW&bug_status=ASSIGNED&bug_status=REOPENED&cmdtype=doit">
<!--
<a href="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&short_desc=%5Bplan&classification=DSDP&product=Target+Management&bug_status=UNCONFIRMED&bug_status=NEW&bug_status=ASSIGNED&bug_status=REOPENED&cmdtype=doit>
-->
TM Project plan items</a> bugzilla query for an up-to-date list.
See the corresponding bugzilla items for up-to-date status information on
ongoing work and planned delivery milestones.
</p>
<p>The current status of each plan item is noted:
</p>
<ul>
  <li><b>Committed</b> plan item - A committed plan item is one that we have
    decided to address for the release.</li>
  <li><b>Proposed</b> plan item - A proposed plan item is one that we are
    considering addressing for the release. Although we are actively
    investigating it, we are not yet in a position to commit to it, or to say
    that we won't be able to address it. After due consideration, a proposal
    will either be committed or deferred.</li>
  <li><b>Deferred</b> plan item - A reasonable proposal that will not make it in
    to this release for some reason is marked as deferred with a brief note as
    to why it was deferred. Deferred plan items may resurface as committed plan
    items at a later point.</li>
</ul>
    ]]></preamble>

<!-- ++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++ -->
<!-- ++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++ -->

    <theme name="Cleanup API">
      <description>
Cleaning up our API's is a prime goal for TM 3.0 in order to limit our
API's to a self-contained, understandable core set and make them 
maintainable in the future.
      </description>
      <committed bugzilla="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&amp;short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;short_desc=%5Bapi%5D%20%5Bbreaking%5D&amp;classification=DSDP&amp;product=Target+Management&amp;component=Core&amp;component=RSE&amp;component=Terminal&amp;target_milestone=3.0&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M3&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M4&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M5&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M6&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M7&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC1&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC2&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC3&amp;long_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;long_desc=&amp;bug_file_loc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;bug_file_loc=&amp;status_whiteboard_type=allwordssubstr&amp;status_whiteboard=&amp;keywords_type=allwords&amp;keywords=&amp;priority=P1&amp;priority=P2&amp;priority=P3&amp;priority=P4&amp;emailtype1=substring&amp;email1=&amp;emailtype2=substring&amp;email2=&amp;bugidtype=include&amp;bug_id=&amp;votes=&amp;chfieldfrom=&amp;chfieldto=Now&amp;chfieldvalue=&amp;cmdtype=doit&amp;order=Reuse+same+sort+as+last+time&amp;field0-0-0=noop&amp;type0-0-0=noop&amp;value0-0-0="></committed>
      <proposed></proposed>
      <deferred bugzilla=""></deferred>
    </theme>
    <theme name="Fix and improve the EFS provider">
      <description>
The RSE EFS provider is an important piece of integration for other projects
to get access to remote resources. It needs to work reliably and with
good performance.
      </description>
      <committed bugzilla="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&amp;short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;short_desc=%5Befs%5D&amp;classification=DSDP&amp;product=Target+Management&amp;component=Core&amp;component=RSE&amp;component=Terminal&amp;target_milestone=3.0&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M3&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M4&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M5&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M6&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M7&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC1&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC2&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC3&amp;long_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;long_desc=&amp;bug_file_loc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;bug_file_loc=&amp;status_whiteboard_type=allwordssubstr&amp;status_whiteboard=&amp;keywords_type=allwords&amp;keywords=&amp;priority=P1&amp;priority=P2&amp;priority=P3&amp;priority=P4&amp;emailtype1=substring&amp;email1=&amp;emailtype2=substring&amp;email2=&amp;bugidtype=include&amp;bug_id=&amp;votes=&amp;chfieldfrom=&amp;chfieldto=Now&amp;chfieldvalue=&amp;cmdtype=doit&amp;order=Reuse+same+sort+as+last+time&amp;field0-0-0=noop&amp;type0-0-0=noop&amp;value0-0-0="></committed>
      <proposed></proposed>
      <deferred bugzilla=""></deferred>
    </theme>
    <theme name="Integrate RSE with the Terminal">
      <description>
The RSE's Command View is missing terminal emulation. A Terminal
integration should make the existing Terminal widget available 
from RSE.
      </description>
      <committed bugzilla="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&amp;short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;short_desc=%5Brseterminal%5D&amp;classification=DSDP&amp;product=Target+Management&amp;component=Core&amp;component=RSE&amp;component=Terminal&amp;target_milestone=3.0&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M3&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M4&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M5&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M6&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M7&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC1&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC2&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC3&amp;long_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;long_desc=&amp;bug_file_loc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;bug_file_loc=&amp;status_whiteboard_type=allwordssubstr&amp;status_whiteboard=&amp;keywords_type=allwords&amp;keywords=&amp;priority=P1&amp;priority=P2&amp;priority=P3&amp;priority=P4&amp;emailtype1=substring&amp;email1=&amp;emailtype2=substring&amp;email2=&amp;bugidtype=include&amp;bug_id=&amp;votes=&amp;chfieldfrom=&amp;chfieldto=Now&amp;chfieldvalue=&amp;cmdtype=doit&amp;order=Reuse+same+sort+as+last+time&amp;field0-0-0=noop&amp;type0-0-0=noop&amp;value0-0-0="></committed>
      <proposed></proposed>
      <deferred bugzilla=""></deferred>
    </theme>
    <theme name="Avoid plugin activation and Improve Performance">
      <description>
RSE should activate plugins only when necessary, and work with
good overall performance.
      </description>
      <committed bugzilla="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&amp;short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;short_desc=%5Bperformance%5D&amp;classification=DSDP&amp;product=Target+Management&amp;component=Core&amp;component=RSE&amp;component=Terminal&amp;target_milestone=3.0&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M3&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M4&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M5&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M6&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M7&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC1&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC2&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC3&amp;long_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;long_desc=&amp;bug_file_loc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;bug_file_loc=&amp;status_whiteboard_type=allwordssubstr&amp;status_whiteboard=&amp;keywords_type=allwords&amp;keywords=&amp;priority=P1&amp;priority=P2&amp;priority=P3&amp;priority=P4&amp;emailtype1=substring&amp;email1=&amp;emailtype2=substring&amp;email2=&amp;bugidtype=include&amp;bug_id=&amp;votes=&amp;chfieldfrom=&amp;chfieldto=Now&amp;chfieldvalue=&amp;cmdtype=doit&amp;order=Reuse+same+sort+as+last+time&amp;field0-0-0=noop&amp;type0-0-0=noop&amp;value0-0-0="></committed>
      <proposed></proposed>
      <deferred bugzilla=""></deferred>
    </theme>
    <theme name="Other">
      <description>
Features and bugs that we plan to address in the next three months that are not yet categorized into a theme.
	  </description>
      <proposed bugzilla="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&amp;short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;short_desc=&amp;classification=DSDP&amp;product=Target+Management&amp;component=Core&amp;component=RSE&amp;component=Terminal&amp;target_milestone=3.0&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M3&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M4&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M5&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M6&amp;target_milestone=3.0+M7&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC1&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC2&amp;target_milestone=3.0+RC3&amp;long_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;long_desc=&amp;bug_file_loc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;bug_file_loc=&amp;status_whiteboard_type=allwordssubstr&amp;status_whiteboard=&amp;keywords_type=allwords&amp;keywords=&amp;priority=P1&amp;priority=P2&amp;priority=P3&amp;priority=P4&amp;emailtype1=substring&amp;email1=&amp;emailtype2=substring&amp;email2=&amp;bugidtype=include&amp;bug_id=&amp;votes=&amp;chfieldfrom=&amp;chfieldto=Now&amp;chfieldvalue=&amp;cmdtype=doit&amp;order=Reuse+same+sort+as+last+time&amp;field0-0-0=short_desc&amp;type0-0-0=notregexp&amp;value0-0-0=%5E%5C%5B%5BA-Z%5D"></proposed>
    </theme>
  </themes_and_priorities>
<!--  <appendix name="Appendix"><![CDATA[
  ]]></appendix> -->  
</plan>